

CONTACT ME AT

Crescent Park

Townvilla, Bandar Bukit Mahkota, 43000, Kajang, Selangor.



afiqahanafiah@gmail.com



+019-6873356

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• Analytical Analysis

●●●● Account Reconciliation

•••• Multitasking Skill

•••• Microsoft Suite

•••• Mathematical Skill

AWARDS RECEIVED

Dean's List, 2020/2021

Best Speaker of Malay Debate, 2020

REFERENCES



<u>Syafiq Harun</u>

Assistant Manager from iCIMB | +017-2816779

Rachel Chang

Finance Manager from Happy Fresh | +012-6302785

AFIQAH HANAFIAH

FINANCE EXECUTIVE

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a university graduate in Bachelor of Science with Honours (Actuarial Science and Risk Management) with one year experience in account reconciliation, proof sheet balancing and streamlining account. Possess high value of soft skills and hard skills. I am a fast learner who willing to learn and explore new experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Apprentice

CIMB Group (iCIMB) - Group Operation - Business Operation Management - Business Transactions | Aug 2021 - Apr 2022

- Analyses and Reconciles balance sheet on daily basis.
- Posting journals into Oracle General Ledger by using ADI (Application Desktop Integrator).
- Preparing and massaging data to update on Masterlist.
- Preparing Memo for RENTAS Settlement.
- Projects Involved: Visa Proof Sheet, Cirrus and Visa Plus Working, Debit Card Refund, Mastercard RENTAS.

Internship

Happy Fresh Malaysia - Finance Department | Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

- Daily data updates on Microsoft Excel.
- Performs bank reconciliation on daily basis.
- Analyses fraud transactions.
- Journals and invoices creation for month end business closing.
- Project involved: Performed all activities for partner store Lotus's Malaysia.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Islamic Science University of Malaysia

Bachelor of Science with Honours (Actuarial Science and Risk Management) | 2017 - 2021

- Minor in Financial Mathematics.
- Completed thesis titled Relationship of Investor Attention and Stock Volatility using Panel Data Regression.

Matriculation College

Science Module 1 | 2016 - 2017

• Studied pure science; Physics, Biology, Chemistry and Mathematics.